{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "How many times does the ball have to be pitched outside of the strike zone before the batter is walked?",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "What is the oldest team in Major League Baseball?",
            "answer": "Atlanta Braves"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "How many srikes are an out?",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "How many MLB teams have homes in New York?",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which team is from Boston?",
            "answer": "Red Sox"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which team is from Baltimore?",
            "answer": "Cardinals"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What are the two teams from Chicago?",
            "answer": "White Sox and Cubs"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which team is from Cleveland",
            "answer": "Indians"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What is the home city for the Tigers?",
            "answer": "Detriot"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What is the home city for the Astros",
            "answer": "Houston"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which team is from Kansas City?",
            "answer": "Royals"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What is the home city for the Athletics?",
            "answer": "Oakland"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which team is from Toronto?",
            "answer": "Blue Jays"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What was the last year the Red Sox won the World Series?",
            "answer": "2013"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What was the last year the Yankees won the World Series?",
            "answer": "2009"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "When did the Cubs finally win the world series?",
            "answer": "2016"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "How many times have the Red Sox won the world Series?",
            "answer": "8"
        }

    ]
}